Alex Laties

387 Franklin Avenue, Apt 103 Brooklyn, NY 11238 Phone: 267 825 2530

Website: http://alex.laties.info/ E-Mail: alex@laties.info Github: https://github.com/alex-laties

General Purpose Software Developer

I'm general purpose programmer who has worked on building, maintaining, and scaling web applications. I work primarily in Python, but have no strong language preference and have used C, C#, Java, Ruby, PHP, and Javascript. I have experience with larger IDEs, such as Visual Studio, MonoDevelop, and XCode, but claim no great proficiencies.

I have worked with teams in an agile style to quickly deliver features and products. I have worked with ticketing systems, such as Jira and Trello, to manage work loads. I have worked with source control systems, like Subversion and Git. I have experience with Test Driven Development through the use of unit tests.

I have contributed some code to open source projects Bottle, watchwithme, and pyrollbar.

Work History

		Work History	
March 2012 - October 2013	Voxy, Inc	Software Engineer	 Worked with Django 1.3 on Python 2.7 to maintain a web application and mobile API. Built prototypes for internal CRMs. Built a new mobile API stack in Bottle. Set up loadbalancing for web and mobile stacks using haproxy and pacemaker. Set up and wrote initial recipes for Chef provisioning service. Also dealt with PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Varnish, Celery, Redis, uwsgi, gunicorn, and nginx.
Fall/Winter 2010 - January 2011	University of Pennsylvania - School of Medicine	Lab Assistant	 Assisted in the generation, collection, and processing of data from experiments. Dealt with Matlab, Excel, and Python, as well as a variety of lab equipment.

Education

Fall 2007 -	
Spring 2010	

University of Pennsylvania -School of Engineering Majored in Computer Science. Learned some theory, implemented a CPU, an OS shell, and some sweet buffer overflows. Also a little Chinese. Dropped out due to health reasons.